{
  "Name": "Spanish",
  "Cards": [
    {
      "Front": "Hello",
      "Back": "Hola",
      "Interval": 1,
      "EaseFactor": 2.5,
      "NextReview": "2025-10-30T13:19:19.4123459+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    },
    {
      "Front": "Goodbye",
      "Back": "Adi\uFFFDs",
      "Interval": 2,
      "EaseFactor": 2.65,
      "NextReview": "2025-10-31T13:19:30.1415237+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    },
    {
      "Front": "Please",
      "Back": "Por favor",
      "Interval": 0,
      "EaseFactor": 2.2499999999999996,
      "NextReview": "2025-10-30T09:10:33.9784416+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    },
    {
      "Front": "Thank you",
      "Back": "Gracias",
      "Interval": 1,
      "EaseFactor": 2.5,
      "NextReview": "2025-10-30T13:19:22.7732154+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    },
    {
      "Front": "Yes",
      "Back": "S\uFFFD",
      "Interval": 2,
      "EaseFactor": null,
      "NextReview": "2025-10-31T13:19:14.1312966+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    },
    {
      "Front": "No",
      "Back": "No",
      "Interval": 2,
      "EaseFactor": 2.2,
      "NextReview": "2025-10-31T13:19:43.6202383+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    },
    {
      "Front": "Water",
      "Back": "Agua",
      "Interval": 2,
      "EaseFactor": 2.65,
      "NextReview": "2025-10-31T13:19:15.7403091+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    },
    {
      "Front": "Food",
      "Back": "Comida",
      "Interval": 4,
      "EaseFactor": 2.6,
      "NextReview": "2025-11-02T13:19:26.1512959+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    },
    {
      "Front": "Friend",
      "Back": "Amigo/Amiga",
      "Interval": 0,
      "EaseFactor": 2.15,
      "NextReview": "2025-10-30T09:08:22.5123011+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    },
    {
      "Front": "House",
      "Back": "Casa",
      "Interval": 0,
      "EaseFactor": 2.5999999999999996,
      "NextReview": "2025-10-30T09:08:23.4226926+01:00",
      "IsNew": false
    }
  ]
}